{
    "id": "d6682a705dc64c8b90bf6ef001c7a260",
    "title": "See, Look, Watch",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. something over there.",
            "description": "We do not normally use the progressive forms of see when it means perceive with one’s eyes.",
            "answers": [
                "am seeing",
                "can see",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0993e49be4947ce8767ce41c2389830"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘……………………….! An elephant!’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "See",
                "Look",
                "Watch"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3451e0cf2d2f49c890b6671f96bb7670"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I have got a problem.’ ‘I ……………………….’",
            "description": "I see can mean I understand.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "look",
                "watch"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0c16da46b9f4ee998cd28cfd2866e2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will ………………………….. that tomorrow.",
            "description": "See about can mean consider.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "see about",
                "watch about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9221e0d77db4ef18f468ff064ec395c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. the attorney tomorrow.",
            "description": "When see means meet, progressive forms are possible.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "will see"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "969a0925c85a403397ed3bccb93baf86"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly I ………………………….. something absolutely marvelous.",
            "description": "See can mean perceive with eyes.",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "looked at",
                "watched"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fe534bdc12cb4d1d8861699d5bb098d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ……………………….. the girl with eyes full of admiration.",
            "description": "To look at something or somebody is to pay attention.",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "looked at",
                "watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9e70a33f359440a83936ef8d5a57300"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘………………………….. the board.’",
            "description": "Before an object, we use look at.",
            "answers": [
                "Look at",
                "See",
                "Watch",
                "Look"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15d5079faae94f44a9b634d770b295f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you ………………………….. me like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "looking",
                "looking at",
                "seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a1e414adccf44fc84ee823f4a98bea6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police have been …………………………… him for a while.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "looking",
                "watching"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "81d2a8ed2ac342d39f153d5dd402db8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. a great movie yesterday.",
            "description": "Watch and see are both used to talk about TV programs and films.",
            "answers": [
                "looked at",
                "watched",
                "saw"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "47336ff61cbf4a518e3e50747c62d5c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. if that color suits you.",
            "description": "See can be used in the sense of find out. It is followed by if/whether.",
            "answers": [
                "See",
                "Look",
                "Watch"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d57b6c2fabf3454fb216ff7a79c7502b"
        }
    ]
}